Register of the Aleksandr Polovet͡s papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- REVIEWS OF ALEXANDER POLOVETS' BOOKS, 1995-2014, undated
  - Set 2 – Publications in other newspapers and magazines
    - Safronova, Elena. "Parodiia bez shutok," Nezavisimaiia gazeta, 2009 September 10 (Box-folder 8: 35)
      Printout from http://exlibris.ng.ru/lit/2009-09-10/5_parodia.html
    - Gladilin, Anatolii. "Predislovie," printed copy, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 36)
    - Fadeeva, Iuliia. "Ia dlia tebia pridumaiu slova, kotorykh nikomu ne govoril," Moskovskii sokol, photocopy, undated (Box-folder 8: 37)
    - Unidentified. Photocopy of fragment from a Swedish article mentioning Alexander Polovet͡s and Almanach-Panorama, undated (Box-folder 8: 38)
    - Cherveniak, Andrei. "Slovatsko-russkie literaturnye kontakty," photocopy, undated (Box-folder 8: 39)
- PANORAMA OFFICE FILE, 1981-2009
  See OVERSIZE FILE.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1992-2013
  Arranged alphabetically by heading.
  - Friends of the Israel Defense Forces (FIDF), 2003-2013 (Box-folder 9: 1)
    Calendar and Saving Lives Gala souvenir program.
  - Jewish Life TV, 2009, undated (Box-folder 9: 2)
    Proposal to add weekly program of interest to the Russian-speaking Jewish community.
  - Pervyi Professional’nyi Bank, 1995 May 9 (Box-folder 9: 3)
    Press material regarding the bank’s sponsorship of the Victory Day parade on Red Square.
  - Poetry, 1992-1993, undated (Box-folder 9: 4)
    Poetry by Thomas Greening and translations into Russian by Sergei Samborskii.
  - Posev magazine conference, 1999 March 22-24 (Box-folder 9: 5)
    Theses of presentation by A. Iu. Shtromas.
  - Sobolev, Georgii Aleksandrovich, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 9: 6)
    Memoirs of and letter from Alexander Polovets’ brother-in-law.
  - Union State of Belarus and Russia, 2002 (Box-folder 9: 7)
- PRINTED MATTER, 1983-2003, undated
  Russian-language journal and newspaper issues, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Journals, 1993-1999
    - Fakt (Los Angeles), No. 19 (43), 1995 October 20 - November 3 (Box-folder 9: 8)
    - Krasnaia burda (Ekaterinburg), No. 5 (70), 1999 (Box-folder 9: 9)
    - Russian Magazine, The (Beverly Hills, CA), 1996 May (Box-folder 9: 10)
    - Serebrianaia mysh' (Moscow), 1993 October (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Newspaper issues, 1983-2003, undated
- OVERSIZE FILE, 1980-2015, undated
  Large-size biographical material, writings, reviews of books by Alexander Polovet͡s, Panorama office file, and printed matter, arranged by physical form.
  - Biographical file, 1999-2015
    - Birthday greetings, 2000-2015
      - "Aleksandru Polovtsu – 65 let!," Tut i Tam, 2000 July 17-31 (Box-folder 10: 1)
      - "Aleksandru Polovtsu 80 let," Panorama, No. 1787, clipping, 2015 July 8-14 (Box-folder 10: 2)
    - Interviews and press coverage, 1999-2003
      - "Mesto vstrechi – Moskva," Panorama, No. 950, clipping, 1999 June 23-29 (Box-folder 10: 3)
      - Tugend, Tom. "L.A.’s Jewish Movers and Shakers," The Jewish Journal of Greater Los Angeles, clipping, 1999 October 22-28 (Box-folder 10: 4)
      - Labunskii, Valentin. "Russkii dukh v amerikanskom plavil’nom kotle," Russkii bazar (New York), clipping, 2000 September 7-13 (Box-folder 10: 5)
      - Gladilin, Anatolii. "Utro krasit nezhnym svetom," Panorama, No. 1138, clipping, 2003 January 29 - February 4 (Box-folder 10: 6)
      - Gladilin, Anatolii. "Solei! Solei!" Panorama, No. 1168, clipping, 2003 August 27 - September 2 (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - Writings, 1980-2015, undated
    - Set 2 - Publications in Panorama (Los Angeles, Ca), 1980-2015, undated
      - "Anatolii Fedoseev, avtor Al'ternativy," photocopy, undated (1984) (Box-folder 10: 8)
      - "Iz Evropy s liubov'iu," photocopy, undated (Box-folder 10: 9)
      - "Kto vy, Edichka?," Panorama, No. 17, photocopy, 1981 July 23 (Box-folder 10: 10)
      - "Sasha Sokolov govorit," Panorama, No. 21, photocopy, 1981 September 3 (Box-folder 10: 11)
        The article’s beginning (pp. 8-9) is missing.
      - "Konets emigratsii?," Panorama, No. 23, clipping, 1981 September 17 (Box-folder 10: 12)
      - "Razgovor s kommentatorom (Brius Khershenzon)," Panorama, No. 25, photocopy, 1981 October 1 (Box-folder 10: 13)
      - "Senator Dzhekson otvechaet na voprosy Panoramy," Panorama, No. 3, photocopy, 1981 December 19-25 (Box-folder 10: 14)
      - "Interv'iu s zamom shefa politsii," Panorama, No. 48, photocopy, 1982 March 13-20 (Box-folder 10: 15)
        The article’s beginning (p. 1) is missing.
      - "Konets eksperimenta," Panorama, No. 57, clipping, 1982 May 14-21 (Box-folder 10: 16)
      - "Sud'ba knigi, sud'ba pisatelia… (Lev Khalif)," Panorama, No. 108, photocopy, 1983 May 6-13 (Box-folder 10: 17)
      - "Neistovyi Kakhane," Panorama, No. 114, photocopy, 1983 June 17-24 (Box-folder 10: 18)
        The article’s conclusion is missing.
      - "Vladimir Sakharov – gody na Zapade," Panorama, No. 155, photocopy, 1984 March 30 - April 6 (Box-folder 10: 19)
        The article’s conclusion (p. 30) is missing.
      - "Poznai sebia, chelovek… Parapsikholog rasskazyvaet," Panorama, No. 158, photocopy, 1984 April 20-27 (Box-folder 10: 20)
      - "K vykhodu fil'ma 2010," Panorama, No. 189, clipping, 1984 November 23-30 (Box-folder 10: 21)
      - "Razgovor s khudozhnikom. (M. Shemiakin)," Panorama, No. 203, photocopy, 1985 March 1-8 (Box-folder 10: 22)
      - "Nash chelovek v Gollivude," Panorama, No. 270, photocopy, 1986 June 13-20 (Box-folder 10: 23)
      - "Prigovori sebia… (Lev Moroz)," Panorama, No. 275, photocopy, 1986 July 18-25 (Box-folder 10: 24)
      - "Tam, gde nas est'," Panorama, No. 280, clipping, 1986 August 22-29 (Box-folder 10: 25)
      - "Federal'nyi prokuror otvechaet na voprosy Panoramy," Panorama, No. 287, photocopy, 1986 October 10-17 (Box-folder 10: 26)
      - "Tsenoiu svobody… Interv'iu A. Avtorkhanova," Panorama, No. 325, photocopy, 1987 July 3-10 (Box-folder 10: 27)
      - "S zavtrashnim bol'shinstvom," Panorama, No. 451, photocopy, 1989 December 1-8 (Box-folder 10: 28)
      - "Interv'iu s Anatoliem Kashpirovskim," Panorama, No. 470, photocopy, 1990 April 13-20 (Box-folder 10: 29)
      - "Na chto im nash grivennik?...," Panorama, No. 537, clipping, 1991 July 26 - August 2 (Box-folder 10: 30)
      - "Pust' ne budet ból'shikh zabot," Panorama, No. 560, clipping, 1991 December 31 - 1992 January 6 (Box-folder 10: 31)
      - "Za chashkoiu chaia v 'Dvorianskom gnezde'," Panorama, No. 584, printed copy, 1992 June 17-23 (Box-folder 10: 32)
      - "Otsutstvie protivnika – poniatie nadumannoe… Vstrecha s marshalom Kulikovym," Panorama, No. 780, clipping, 1996 March 20-26 (Box-folder 10: 33)
        The conclusion of the article (p. 26) is missing.
      - "Komu budet khuzhe?," Panorama, No. 800, photocopy, 1996 August 7-13 (Box-folder 10: 34)
      - "Eto tozhe terror," Panorama, No. 801, photocopy, 1996 August 14-20 (Box-folder 10: 35)
      - "Shou, za kotoroe my platim," Panorama, No. 802, photocopy, 1996 August 21-27 (Box-folder 10: 36)
      - "O mul'tfil'makh, i ne tol'ko o nikh," Panorama, No. 803, photocopy, 1996 August 28 - September 3 (Box-folder 10: 37)
      - "Kogda podvodit 'firma'," Panorama, No. 804, photocopy, 1996 September 4-10 (Box-folder 10: 38)
      - "Ne tak uzh vse plokho…," Panorama, No. 805, photocopy, 1996 September 11-17 (Box-folder 10: 39)
      - "Kogda prezident ostaetsia…," Panorama, No. 806, photocopy, 1996 September 18-24 (Box-folder 10: 40)
      - "My pomnim Saveliia Kramarova," Panorama, No. 826, photocopy, 1997 February 5-11 (Box-folder 10: 41)
      - "Samyi pechal'nyi fil'm Stivena Spil'berga," Panorama, No. 846, photocopy, 1997 June 25 - July 1 (Box-folder 10: 42)
      - "Golos budet zvuchat'. Golos Ameriki," Panorama, No. 869, photocopy, 1997 December 3-9 (Box-folder 10: 43)
      - "Drugogo globusa u nas net…," Panorama, No. 887, clipping, 1998 April 8-14 (Box-folder 10: 44)
      - "Kto na kogo vliiaet… Iz besedy s Bulatom Okudzhavoi" and "Togda opusteet Parizh," Panorama, No. 943, clipping, 1999 May 5-11 (Box-folder 10: 45)
      - "Khot' pokhozhe na Rossiiu… Nash drug A. Gorodnitskii," Panorama, No. 1000 and No. 1001, photocopy, 2000 June 7-13 and June 14-20 (Box-folder 10: 46)
      - "Gde tak vol'no dyshit chelovek," Panorama, No. 1026 and No. 1027, photocopy, 2000 December 6-12 and December 13-19 (Box-folder 10: 47)
      - "Bozhe, blagoslovi Ameriku…," Panorama, No. 1047, clipping, 2001 May 2-8 (Box-folder 10: 48)
      - "Zhutkoe delo. Iz rasskazov postradavshego," Panorama, No. 1124, photocopy, 2002 October 23-29 (Box-folder 10: 49)
      - "Zazerkal'e. (Mezhdu proshlym i budushchim)," Panorama, No. 1144, clipping, 2003 March 12-18 (Box-folder 10: 50)
      - "Prem'era v 'Prem'ere'," Panorama, No. 1256, clipping., 2005 May 5-11 (Box-folder 10: 51)
        Written under the pseudonym "Aleks Daniel'."
      - "Tam, za ekranom…," Panorama, No. 1265, clipping, 2005 July 6-12 (Box-folder 10: 52)
      - "Obalduevshchina. Skazka dlia vsekh vozrastov," Panorama, No. 1312, clipping, 2006 May 31 - June 6 (Box-folder 10: 53)
      - "Kukla po imeni Elizabet," Panorama, No. 1330, photocopy, 2006 October 4-10 (Box-folder 10: 54)
      - "Svidetel'stva," Panorama, No. 1358, photocopy, 2007 April 18-24 (Box-folder 10: 55)
      - "Breget," Panorama, No. 1383, photocopy, 2007 October 10-16 (Box-folder 10: 56)
      - "K iubileiu druga. (L. Shargorodskii)," Panorama, No. 1489, clipping, 2009 October 21-27 (Box-folder 10: 57)
      - "Est' v druzhbe schast'e ogolteloe… K iubileiu Anatoliia Gladilina," Panorama, No. 1534, clipping, 2010 September 1-7 (Box-folder 10: 58)
      - "Tri knigi – tri sud'by," Panorama, No. 1545, clipping, 2010 November 17-23 (Box-folder 10: 59)
      - "'Moi kartiny – moi deti', ili V stile Leonida Stilia," Panorama, No. 1546, clipping, 2010 November 24-30 (Box-folder 10: 60)
      - "Liubite li vy teatr? O spektakle Room Service v Santa-Monike," Panorama, No. 1557, clipping, 2011 February 9-15 (Box-folder 10: 61)
      - "Atlantida, liubov' moia… K 80-letiiu Aleksandra Gorodnitskogo," Panorama, No. 1669, clipping, 2013 April 3-9 (Box-folder 10: 62)
      - "Proshchai, Moskva?" Panorama, No. 1701, clipping, 2013 November 13-19 (Box-folder 10: 63)
      - "Iz predisloviia k 'Fotoletopisi'," Panorama, No. 1733, clipping, 2014 June 25 - July 1 (Box-folder 10: 64)
      - "Ne khlebom edinym… (A. Gurevich)," Panorama, No. 1760, clipping, 2014 December 31 - 2015 January 6 (Box-folder 10: 65)
      - "Druz'ia! (Obrashchenie ot Fonda Okudzhavy)," Panorama, No. 1772, clipping, 2015 March 25-31 (Box-folder 10: 66)
    - Set 3 - Publications in Post-Soviet Russia and Russian-language press in the United States, 1995-2005
      - "Kongress russkoi pressy. Vmesto poslesloviia," Izvestiia, photocopy, 1999 June 29 (Box-folder 10: 67)
      - "Bulat. Dlia chego ia zdes'," Literaturnaia iarmarka (Moscow), No. 12, clipping, 2005 May (Box-folder 10: 68)
    - Set 4 - Publications in the Russian-language press in the United States, other countries and on the Internet, undated
      - "Na zemle etoi vechnoi on zhil," Russkii bazar, No. 51, photocopy, undated (December 14-20) (Box-folder 10: 69)
      - "Sem' zhiznei Vladimira Kunina," Russkii Magazin, clipping, undated (Box-folder 10: 70)
  - Reviews of Alexander Polovet͡s' books, 1989-2015
    - Golovskoi, Valerii. "Kogda publitsistika stanovitsia literaturoi," Russkaia mysl' (Paris), printed copy, 1989 August 11 (Box-folder 11: 1)
    - Sebelev, Aleksandr. "Iz SSSR v Turtsiiu na rezinovoi lodke," Panorama, No. 1417, printed copy, 2008 June 4-10 (Box-folder 11: 2)
    - Kuzovleva, Tat'iana. "Vechera pod chasami, idushchimi vspiat'," Panorama, No. 1451, printed copy, 2009 January 28 - February 3 (Box-folder 11: 3)
    - Nerpina, Galina. "Kogda vozvrashchaetsia veter," Panorama, No. 1462, printed copy, 2009 April 15-21 (Box-folder 11: 4)
    - Gelein, Aleksei. "Obladaia talantom, nado stat' emigrantom," Panorama, No. 1465, printed copy and typescript, 2009 May 6-12 (Box-folder 11: 5)
    - Pis'mennyi, M. "Po-druzheski otkryto," Panorama, No. 1471, printed copy, 2009 June 17-23 (Box-folder 11: 6)
    - Zheleznova, Nadezhda. "Mezhdu proshlym i budushchem," Panorama, No. 1473, printed copy and typescript, 2009 July 1-7 (Box-folder 11: 7)
    - "Vseamerikanskii kul'turnyi fond Bulata Okudzhava," Panorama, No. 1576, printed copy, 2011 June 22-28 (Box-folder 11: 8)
    - Kuzovleva, Tat'iana. "Vechera pod chasami, idushchimi vspiat'," Panorama, No. 1687, printed copy, 2013 August 7-13 (Box-folder 11: 9)
    - Gelein, Aleksei. "Emigratsiia v sebia," Panorama, No. 1696, printed copy and typescript, 2013 October 9-15 (Box-folder 11: 10)
    - "K vykhodu v svet sobraniia sochinenii Aleksandra Polovtsa," Panorama, No. 1700 and No. 1702, printed copy, 2013 November 6-12 and November 20-26 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Panorama office file, 1981-2009, undated
    - Alphabetic list of authors, 1997 (Box-folder 11: 12)
    - Articles category table, 1997 (Box-folder 11: 13)
    - Articles catalogue by author, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 11: 14-15)
    - Author catalogue by issue, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 11: 16-17)
    - Author lists, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 11: 18)
    - Author and vendor lists, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11: 19-21)
    - Manuscripts submitted by readers, 1988-2009 (Box-folder 11: 22)
    - Miscellany, 1986-1997, undated (Box-folder 11: 23)
      Includes financial estimates for proposed publication of English-language version of Panorama and proposed legal action against Contact newspaper.
  - Printed matter - Newspaper issues, 1983-2003
    - Gollivudskie khroniki (Beverly Hills, CA), No. 1 (8), 1998 (Box-folder 12: 1)
    - Novosti (New York), No. 57, No. 61, No. 81, No. 86, and No. 92, 1983 December 3 and 10, 1984 January 1, 7-13, and 14-21 (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Novyi amerikanets (Jersey City, NJ), No. 199 and No. 221, 1983 December 13 and 1984 May 17 (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - Piatnitsa-Ekspress (Los Angeles, CA), No. 14, 1995 October 13-19 (Box-folder 12: 4)
    - Pravda russkaia i amerikanskaia (West Hollywood, CA), No. 1, 2003 February 12-19 (Box-folder 12: 5)
    - Russkii golos (New York), No. 3, 1984 January 19 (Box-folder 12: 6)
    - Russkii magazin (Cleveland, OH), No. 3 (14), 1995 March (Box-folder 12: 7)
    - Vne zakona (St. Petersburg, Russia), No. 9 (33), 1997 September (Box-folder 12: 8)
- DOUBLE OVERSIZE FILE, 1966-2002
  Extra-large-size writings.
  - Writings
    - Set 1, 1966
      - "Klady v arkhivakh," Moskovskaia pravda, No. 193, clipping, 1966 August 20 (Box-folder 13: 1)
    - Set 3, 1995-2002
      - "Podval," Bostonskoe vremia, No. 46, clipping, 1995 March 1 (Box-folder 13: 2)
      - "Polnotsennyi kompleks predvziatosti," Literaturnaia gazeta, No. 40, clipping, 2002 October 2-8 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Reviews of Alexander Polovet͡s' books, 2006-2009
    - Kuzovleva, Tat'iana. "Sudeb skreshchen'e," Kul'tura, No.32, 2006 August 17-23 (Box-folder 13: 4)
    - Kuzovleva, Tat'iana. "Mesto. Vremia. Vostrebovannost'," Kul'tura, No. 14, 2009 April 9-15 (Box-folder 13: 5)
    - Makovenko, Evgeniia. "Po sledam Sazoniady. Istoriia emigratsii cherez rukopozhatie Aleksandra Polovtsa," Nezavisimaia gazeta, No. 110, clipping, 2009 June 4 (Box-folder 13: 6)
    - Safronova, Elena. "Parodiia bez shutok. Burnyi Potok iz Budushchego v Proshloe," Nezavisimaia gazeta, No. 110, 2009 September 10 (Box-folder 13: 7)
    - Zheleznova, Nadezhda. "Mezhdu proshlym i bydushchem. V "Zebre" izdali knigu Aleksandra Polovtsova," Kul'tura, No. 15, 2009 April 16-22 (Box-folder 13: 8)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1980-2016, undated
  Photographs depicting literary figures, political figures, and political events.
  - Literary figures, 1981-2016, undated
    - Inventory prepared by Alexander Polovets, 2016 (Box-folder 14: 1)
    - Akhmadulina, Bella, undated (Box-folder 14: 2)
      11 color prints depicting Akhmadulina with Alexander Polovets, Boris Messerer, and other people.
    - Aleksin, Anatolii, 1999, undated (Box-folder 14: 3)
      5 color prints depicting Aleksin with Alexander Polovets and other people.
    - Aleshkovsky, Iuz, undated (Box-folder 14: 4)
      9 prints (2 BW and 7 color) depicting Aleshkovsky with Alexander Polovets, Anatoly Gladilin, Ilya Baskin, and other people.
    - Arkanov, Arkady, undated (Box-folder 14: 5)
      12 color prints depicting Arkanov at various events, with Alexander Polovets, Irina Elchina, and other people.
    - Artamonov, Sergei, undated (Box-folder 14: 6)
      2 BW prints depicting Artamonov alone and with Alexander Polovets.
    - Avni, Baruch. See Kamianov, Boris
    - Avtorkhanov, Abdurakhman, undated (Box-folder 14: 7)
      5 color prints depicting Avtorkhanov with Alexander Polovets and other people.
    - Begishev, Valerii, 1994, undated (Box-folder 14: 8)
      5 color prints depicting Begishev with Alexander Polovets and other people.
    - Bitov, Andrei, 1991, undated (Box-folder 14: 9)
      8 color prints depicting Bitov with Alexander Polovets, Olga Matich and other people.
    - Bokov, Nikolai, undated (Box-folder 14: 10)
      3 prints (2 BW and 1 color) depicting Bokov with Alexander Polovets and Panorama staff.
    - Dinner at the home of Alexander Polovets, undated (Box-folder 14: 11)
      3 large prints depicting Vyacheslav Ivanov, Svetlana Ivanov, Alexander Polovets and his wife. These prints are not listed in the inventory prepared by Alexander Polovets.
    - Dobrodeev, Boris, undated (Box-folder 14: 11)
      1 color print depicting Dobrodeev with Alexander Polovets.
    - Dovlatov, Sergei, undated (Box-folder 14: 12)
      4 prints (1 BW and 3 color) depicting Dovlatov with Alexander Polovets, Dmitri Bobyshev, and other people.
    - Erofeyev, Victor, undated (Box-folder 14: 13)
      3 color prints depicting Erofeyev alone and autographing books.
    - Gendelev, Mikhail, undated (Box-folder 14: 14)
      2 color prints depicting Gendelev with Mark Popovksy and Alexander Polovets.
    - Gladd, James, 1966 (Box-folder 14: 15)
      1 color print depicting Gladd with Alexander Polovets.
    - Gorodnitsky, Alexander, 1999, undated (Box-folder 14: 16)
      11 color prints.
    - Grafov, Eduard, undated (Box-folder 14: 17)
      1 color print depicting Grafov with Valerii Begishev, Alexander Polovets and Shota Tvaradze.
    - Grich, Aleksandr, 1987, undated (Box-folder 14: 18)
      3 color prints depicting Grich with Alexander Polovets, Igor Guberman, and other people.
    - Guberman, Igor, 1999-2000, undated (Box-folder 14: 19)
      10 color prints depicting Guberman with Alexander Polovets, Anatoly Gladilin, Mark Rozovsky, and other people.
    - Group photograph, undated (Box-folder 14: 20)
      1 print depicting (left to right) Mihajlo Mihajlov, Ilya Levin, Vasily Aksyonov, Ira Straus and Vladimir Matlin.
    - Irteniev, Igor, undated (Box-folder 14: 21)
      1 color print depicting Irteniev with Aleksei and Alla Kiskachi.
    - Iskander, Fazil, undated (Box-folder 14: 22)
      3 color prints depicting Iskander alone, with Alexander Polovets and Leonid Frank, and with other people.
    - Ivanov, Alexander, undated (Box-folder 14: 23)
      3 color prints depicting Ivanov with Alexander Polovets and Bulat Okudzhava.
    - Ivanov, Vyacheslav, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14: 24)
      2 color prints depicting Ivanov with his wife Svetlana and with Alexander Gorodnitsky.
    - Kamianov, Boris, undated (Box-folder 14: 25)
      3 prints (1 BW and 2 color) depicting Kamianov with Alexander Polovets in Israel and Kamianov reading from his poetry in Moscow.
    - Kandel, Feliks, undated (Box-folder 14: 26)
      3 color prints depicting Kandel with Alexander Polovets and Iakov Skliansky.
    - Kazakova, Rimma, undated (Box-folder 14: 27)
      1 color print depicting Kazakova with Alexander Polovets, Tatiana Kuzovleva, and A. Rakhmanina.
    - Kirshon, Jr., Vladimir, undated (Box-folder 14: 28)
      1 color print depicting Kirshon by Alexander Polovets’ swimming pool.
    - Kopelev, Lev, 1985 (Box-folder 14: 29)
      1 BW print depicting Kopelev with three women after a performance in Ann Arbor, MI.
    - Korzhavin, Naum, undated (Box-folder 14: 30)
      3 prints (1 BW and 2 color) depicting Korzhavin with Alexander Polovets and with Panorama staff.
    - Kozlovsky, Vladimir, undated (Box-folder 14: 31)
      2 color prints depicting Kozlovsky at work and with one of his readers.
    - Kunin, Vladimir, undated (Box-folder 14: 32)
      11 color prints depicting Kunin at home in Moscow, in the Panorama offices, with Alexander Polovets and other people.
    - Kuzovleva, Tatiana, 2007-2008, undated (Box-folder 14: 33)
      2007-2008 and undated. 7 color prints depicting Kuzovleva with Alexander Polovets and other people.
    - Latynina, Yulia, undated (late 1990s) (Box-folder 14: 34)
      2 color prints depicting Latynina on Rodeo Drive in Beverly Hills with Alexander Polovets.
    - Levchenko, Stanislav, 1994 (Box-folder 14: 35)
      1 color print depicting Levchenko with Alexander Polovets in San Francisco.
    - Limonov, Edward, undated (Box-folder 14: 36-38)
    - Logachev, Viktor, undated (Box-folder 14: 39)
      1 color print depicting Logachev at the home of Alexander Polovets.
    - Lvov, Arkadii, undated (Box-folder 14: 40)
      1 color print depicting Lvov with Mikhail Vishnevsky and Sergei Rakhlin at the offices of Panorama.
    - Mak, Leonid, undated (Box-folder 14: 41)
      1 color print depicting Mak performing in San Diego.
    - Maximov, Vladimir, undated (Box-folder 14: 42)
      3 color prints depicting Maximov with Mikhail Shifutinsky, Gabriel Valk, and Rachael Valk.
    - Mechik, Donat, undated (Box-folder 14: 43)
      1 color print depicting Mechik with his daughter Ksana.
    - Mihajlov, Mihajlo, undated (Box-folder 14: 44)
      1 color print depicting Mihajlov with Alexander Genis and Ilya Levin.
    - Mnatsakanian, Sergei, undated (Box-folder 14: 45)
      2 color prints depicting Mnatsakanian at a writers’ meeting in Moscow and with Tatiana Kuzovleva.
    - Muravieva, Irina, 1994, undated (Box-folder 14: 46)
      5 color prints depicting Muravieva alone, with Alexander Polovets, with Nikolai Puschkarsky and Leonid Khotin.
    - Nadein, Vladimir, 1995, undated (Box-folder 14: 47)
      4 color prints depicting Nadein alone, with Alexander Polovets, and with Larisa and Efim Tovbin.
    - Nekrasov, Viktor, undated (Box-folder 14: 48)
      3 prints (1 BW and 2 color) depicting Nekrasov being interviewed by Sergei Levin with the artist Krasniansky and other people.
    - Nudelman, Rafail, undated (Box-folder 14: 49)
      1 color print depicting Nudelman with Alexander Polovets.
    - Oislander, Iurii, undated (Box-folder 14: 50)
      2 BW prints depicting Oislander at breakfast and carrying a sack of onions.
    - Okudzhava family, undated (Box-folder 14: 51)
      2 color prints depicting Bulat Okudzhava, Jr. and Olga Okudzhava with Elena Carlisle. Photos were taken in New York.
    - Papernyi, Vadim, 1981 (Box-folder 14: 52)
      1 color print depicting Papernyi with Alexander Polovets and Ilya Baskin.
    - Papernyi, Zinovy, undated (Box-folder 14: 53)
      1 BW print depicting Papernyi with Alexander Polovets.
    - Paramonov, Boris, undated (1986) (Box-folder 14: 54)
      1 color print depicting Paramonov at the 5th anniversary of Panorama.
    - Pasternak, Evgenii Borisovich, undated (Box-folder 14: 55)
      1 color print depicting Pasternak at a performance in Peredelkino at Bulat Okudzhava’s cottage.
    - Perelman, Victor, undated (Box-folder 14: 56)
      2 prints (1 BW and 1 color) depicting Perelman being interviewed at a Slavic conference and sitting in the offices of Panorama.
    - Pirlikh, Andrei, undated (Box-folder 14: 57)
      2 color prints depicting Pirlikh with Alexander Polovets and son.
    - Poliakov, Yuri, 1988 (Box-folder 14: 58)
      1 color print depicting Poliakov with Alexander Polovets.